yo we just blew the whole [__]
account no that's how you closed the
trade
bro we literally just
blew the
whole
account it's week six of me turning $100
into a million and let me tell you you
guys aren't ready for this week and last
week was honestly boring we traded a
whole entire week and we did not take
any trades where the account stayed at
an
$8,900 balance where we missed some
opportunities but we actually avoided a
lot losses this week has just consisted
of dodging bullets we've been off
[__] week the goal for this week is
to turn the $8,000 to $16,000 without
using another tra so at the challenge
it welcome to week six of me trainning
$100
into million now this week is a little
bit different
now we got
views of my [__] Bugatti so if I
don't complete this
challenge I can't afford the Bugatti so
I definitely have to complete the
challenge and stay on Route so the go
doesn't feel right right the Bugatti is
pink I'm wearing
blue I'll be right back give me a
second more like it huh got to be on the
same vibe
as I cannot believe I [__] did that
dude still
surreal what's the payment on one of
those my payment is
46,000 a month and then the insurance is
like 2500 so it comes out to like 48
49,000 every month so yeah we got a lot
of work to do to make that up so let's
start off the 100 to the mill challenge
like always let's go straight into the
myx book to show you guys where we are
right now currently on the balance
currently we have taken the 100 bucks to
$88,000 you guys can see that the
starting balance was 100 bucks and it
was just updated 44 minutes ago down
below over here you can currently see
our win rate is currently a 70% of the
total amount of Trades that we have
taken taken a total seven amount of
Trades and 100% of our trades have been
short we have not taken any long
positions and our average duration is an
interesting 20 hours now this right here
is going to be a problem very soon the
commissions that we have on the account
because the bigger obviously we start
scaling on this challenge the more
slippage the more commission everything
that we're it's going to cost us to
trade so I might be switching Brokers
very very soon not entirely sure just
yet but I will be letting you guys know
if I do well I don't Market a broker I'm
just going to let you guys know if I
switch to a broker I don't plan to
Market any broker anytime soon so with
that being said let's go into the charts
so currently right now let's start off
with Euro GBP Euro GBP currently has a
very clean weekly higher high structure
move as you can see we were creating
lower low lower high lower low and now
we have a higher high where now we're
having a higher low retracement to
potentially have a retracement and
rejection from this point right here
when we go down to the Daily time frame
you can clearly see that the daily time
frame has had so whenever above this
area you can see that price is having a
reac reaction up and whenever we're
above it we're having a reaction up and
up whenever we are under we're having a
push to then the downside so obviously
now we are bullish and now we are above
it what also coincidence that we have a
round psychological level
85,000 along with the daily EMA so you
have weekly area of interest you have
daily area of interest you have round
psychological level you have EMA strong
level support and resistance it just
simply makes more sense to buy this
trade once it gets to this area rather
than not so currently right now looks
like we are having some type of a
reaction from there looks like we are
having a shift the structure and in the
1 hour we are having a potential
inverted Head and Shoulders cuz
obviously it's nowhere near being done
what I want from this trade is for it to
actually make it to this area of
Interest I needed to actually hit it I
need to actually for it to come here it
did not get all the way there if you
notice even when price is over here it
made it just a little bit more just a
little bit more so I'm going to need a
for it to just make it just a little bit
a little bit more down here in order for
me to actually be interested in the
trade but we'll see I don't know I might
be interested in taking the trade now
we'll keep you updated next GBP CHF
probably one of the cleanest ones that
you can probably see and it is this
beautiful higher high higher low higher
high higher low higher high higher low
higher high boom Shi the structure lower
low lower high lower low now this time
frame is bearish now if I just show you
guys this Market structure like this
which is realistically how you have to
look at the structure of the market not
look at the market this right here is
the structure of the market and you can
clearly see how we were creating higher
highs higher lows then we shifted we did
a ginormous and beautifully formated
double top pattern right here and now
we're coming back to retest that
neckline of the double top to then have
a reaction to the downside what a
coincidence that the neckline of the
double top happens to also be at the
weekly EMA and also happens to have a
round psychological level one .1 to 500
which is obviously very key because now
you just have three four things that
simply make sense at this area in order
for you to be interested in the trade
what a coincidence now we also have the
daily EMA we also have daily structure
level so on and so forth so what I'm
going to be waiting for for this trade
is for price to have a break and retest
under this little double top formation
that we're potentially creating at this
area here to have an alarm right at the
bottom of it that's going to notify me
as soon as we break out of it and this
this trade once it does that it's going
to have a great risk reward we can
easily get a 1 to five or even to this
structure point and then obviously we
have a smaller stop loss we get like a 1
to six 1 to6 or. 7 this is a great risk
reward on this trade because we are
following the trend we're trading with
the weekly time frame we're trading with
the daily time frame and once that
double top breaks we're going to be
trading with the 4our time frame so we
have three time frames that are going
all in the same direction simply just
enter the trade set and forget next is
going to be Euro AUD Euro AUD was a
little bit tricky last week and we
avoided multiple losses on it now it
looks like we are making our way down to
this area of Interest where we will be
interested in buying so we were looking
for counter Trend trade shorts but they
just simply did not play out obviously
oh just to show you guys what time is
it what time is it it's currently Monday
so we start out the challenge on Monday
it's currently 9:11 a.m. so on Sunday I
kind of predicted that price was going
to come back and then sell didn't do it
so we're just going to wait for this
trade at this area to then pretty much
buy at this daily dma next is USD CAD
USD CAD we currently had a very strong
push the F the last two weeks that have
pretty much engulf the last two weeks
before that daily time frame we were
rejecting under this area of Interest
daily time frame went bearish rejection
from the EMA just waiting for another
lower high on this Market to take the
trade to the downside so right now we
are clearly at a lower low all I want is
your price to have a lower high retest
structure retest the EMA so then price
can then head to the downside next is
going to be
gbpusd which I'm not entirely sure if
this trade will even do this but would
look fantastic if it does we had a very
strong push last week breaking out of
this channel now we have a higher low
higher high I'm just anticipating for
price to have a pullback retest support
and resistance level so then head to the
upside clearly this is a level very well
respected resistance resistance and then
resistance all the way over here so it's
the same exact Zone we're just waiting
for price to then retest it because we
had the Breakout but we never came back
and retested and what a coincidence if
price starts to then come back and
retest we're going to also retest this
EMA along with this structure point so
then just give it the new higher low to
continue heading to the upside so what I
do here is I simply just set my alarm at
this area so I get notified once the
trade reaches that point next is going
to be nzdusd which truthfully I don't
even like it I'll update you guys if I
do later on throughout the week EUR USD
and gvp CAD so the oh yeah GBP CAD is
the last per that I'm currently
interested in and I want you guys to to
to to look at the market how I'm about
to look at it right now if you're still
paying very close attention to these
analysis and not just looking at it as a
NPC and looking at it briefly and just
wanting to focus where is he going to
enter where is he going to get out
that's not how you're going to become
successful that is not how you're going
to make money and trading that is not
how you're going to [__] afford a
Bugatti I'll tell you that for sure you
have to look at the markets further than
what it is doing right now like you have
to have more of a deeper analysis and
connection with the market that you just
simply have to ask yourself does this
make sense or no and you have to be
realistic with that answer and 99% of
you guys will not be asking yourself
that question and for those of you that
do whatever do you're not going to be
realistic with that answer so you're
never going to be successful in trading
now I'm going to ask you two questions
and you pause the video think about it
and see what I say and see if it makes
sense this market right here all right
cool the does it look bullish right
higher high higher low higher high
higher low what do you think the answer
is probably yes okay so you would be
looking to buy this Market essentially
right the answer is probably yes all
right well let's just look a little bit
to the left real quick and let's see
what the market has done last time it
was at this high so if I look over here
price has not been to a high like this
one since this structure Point here when
I check the date down here on the
structure Point March 20 21 so it has
not been here in about three years
almost four years all right cool let's
keep going to the left when was the last
time the structure actually made it this
far okay this point right here when was
that March
2019 okay cool cool cool let's keep
going when did it actually break out of
it actually broke out of it here when
was that February 18 2018 so a little
bit over 7 years ago so why would you
buy a Market that has not broken through
a strong level of resistance that has
been struggling to break through it for
many many many many years to come and
the one time that it did break it it
just completely changed the trend all
the way down does it make sense to buy
here probably not cuz last time it
literally made it right up to that high
and the structure made it right to 177
500 it did not have the break through it
it had a major reaction from it and I'm
just literally looking at this part
right here and if I move it this way it
looks just like this and what happened
here it went down if I take this and I
go over here it looks the same and what
did it do it went down so yes even
though the trend might be bullish you
have to be very observative to what
price has done to the left because what
happens to the left is going to repeat
itself so not saying Longs aren't the
best thing but I wouldn't say it would
be something I would be fully focused on
due to the fact that we have not been
able to break through this resistance
level here and you're basically buying
right into the highest level of
resistance that the market has been
rejecting from So currently right now
might be interested in some some counter
Trend trades to the downside maybe once
we break under this level I'm going to
be very observative with this one right
I'm going to be very selective because I
do like this I do like this Shi D
structure that's currently happening
right now I definitely see this as a
upwards Channel again I hate using trend
lines but I just like the channel That
it forms so maybe if we have a break out
of that channel retest it I'll be
probably interested in sales so that's
pretty much it for right now currently
market update
9:25 in the morning so I think our goal
this week is uh to see me drift the
Bugatti I want to drift the Bugatti I
don't think anybody's ever done it and
I'm going to do my best to make sure
that goes down safely in a controlled
environment you know what I'm saying so
stay tuned and we'll update you guys in
a bit
all right so Jordan just pulled up right
now so Jordan can't even [__] walk
cuz obviously he's still recuperating
from cancer and he just pulled up right
now driving with like this hand stick
thing that he's doing bro he that looks
like a [__] gun that looks like a gun
sh I don't get shot if I get P yo for
real is it stuck to the pedal yeah stuck
to the pedal only is like it has this
little play it's weird bro it feels
weird it feels weird yeah you feel weird
you want to in the Bugatti yeah I'm down
but you have to like literally like it's
a mission you have to like pick me up
I'll pick you up and like literally like
carry me Dr me down Bro you've done more
missions than them you're
[Music]
I was it dog yeah yeah that sh crazy
this thing is literally the fastest
thing I've been in they want to have
your the
Bugatti um in this warehouse and have
this marching trumps marching band
behind it playing while Kodak and all
them are rapping in front but Trump will
not be there I I mean I've been part of
a couple music videos I know how this
[__] goes you know yeah yeah start pull
up at 3: start at 7 end at 1: in the
morning you
know bro I [__] hope it's not like
that I will see you down there sick all
right I'll see you at that address
tomorrow okay
thank we were supposed to meet Trump
tomorrow but we're going to be Kodak
Black and 42 Doug it's pretty sick you
know you know what's funny I was
actually going to give Kodak Black a
cyber truck at the beginning of the year
but I just couldn't make the connection
and stuff but it's crazy how things turn
around now I'm going to meet Kodak Black
and my Bugatti is going to be in the
music video with Trump which is kind of
[__] sick if you ask me so trade up
dat you know what a trade up dat
right bro I just laugh because it's like
I was just a kid from Dunkin Donuts dude
just literally working a regular N I
wasn't even working a 9 to 5 I was
working a 7 to 3 I was I was being there
at 700 in the morning leaving at 3:00 to
now literally being one step away one
phone call away from the president of
the United States of America I think
it's insane gives me goosebumps it's
it's it's almost surreal how this has
become the new normal in my life but I'm
very grateful because all this was
because of trading because trading would
have trading built the character and the
person that I am today and without
trading being in my life none of this
would have ever been possible so if
you're going out there through a journey
and it's just difficult and you're in
that lonely Journey losing losing losing
and having thoughts of giving up trust
me don't do it there is light at the end
of the tunnel and it will all be worth
it trust me trust me so trade update
currently right now it is 9:00 at night
so I think it's about 12 hours since the
last time we did the last update as you
can see I'm wearing the same clothes I
have not left the house all day
literally been here chilling still no
trade in the account as we speak but we
might enter a trade right now on this
GBP CHF So currently daily time frame
close very very very clean double daily
rejection from this area of Interest I
would have loved it would have made it a
little bit higher but I love how the 4
Hour right now is potentially about to
break on the the structure level which
is going to give us the 1 hour head and
shoulders and then basically we're going
to have the retest of this neckline
right here as soon as we do that so it's
going to be a quick break retest and
then we enter this trade potentially
right so I might enter this trade as
soon as it breaks out through here I
don't know figure it out next is Euro
GBP so we want to enter this trade as
soon as it has the retest of this level
to head to the upside we have not quite
made it there just yet the 4H hour is
Shifting and I do like this it looks
very clean so if we have a nice higher
low shift the structure here then I
would enter the trade so I'm going to
wait for a little bit of a pullback to
enter this trade to the upside um GBP
CHF is the one that we just analyzed
Euro a D not interested USD CAD not
interested GBP USD is the only other one
that I'm interested in which obviously
we're at the higher high still waiting
for that pullback and then lastly is GBP
CAD so we are rejecting that high time
frame rejecting that round psychological
level almost and then the 4-Hour time
frame is slowing down on this pullback
so I might be interested in entering a
counter Trend trade if we do something
like this but
remember every single time I take a
counter Trend trade I'm breaking my
[__] trading plan you know that means
I got to drive the [__]
Punisher you [__] Beetle you you know
what it is that owning a Bugatti
probably the most expensive car you
could buy I have access to and you being
so true to your word that if I don't do
what I'm supposed to do I'm going to
punish myself and not drive my $3
million Bugatti and I'm going to drive
my piece of [__] Beetle that guy I have
a man at my [__] word and I'll show
you guys so now we got Jane juice
pulling up for the podcast but right
before for the podcast we got to drop
off the Bugatti you know what I'm saying
we're going to put some little set and
forget stickers on this video video we
know you got to remember marketing
marketing is key got to spread the brand
of the number one trading strategy in
the world Nam set of forget so we're
going to put C forget stickers all over
the Bugatti for the music video tomorrow
so let's go all right we got J and Juice
in the house run of a pod right now's
going on brother he was waiting on us
for us to do the Pod so we're going to
go real quick to drop off the Bugatti to
do some stickers and then we'll run up
the BT you haven't been in the Bugatti
here right no not yet yeah he was
actually the first person to actually
see and he hasn't r in it yet so we're
going to take him for a ride see his see
his reaction he's he's not
ready I already put 250 Mi on it driving
it what do you feel like bro honestly
now I don't know if this is going to
about I don't know if this is about to
sound [__] up or not dude but I feel
normal right now yeah then if it's a
really good thing then what comes after
like you know let's say I normalize this
so
much that's what I wanted like after the
pot I want remember like the cigar I was
like I I was thinking like we light up a
cigar and I want to talk to you about
this [__] cuz if you got a Bugatti now
like next bro like I hate to break it to
you but next it's it's a private jet
probably like that that's it like that's
the thing and you just have to accept it
and now it's the normal so remember what
I was telling you yesterday all right
you
ready hey hey yo
bro yo I'm numb brother I don't feel
anything n that's crazy no literally it
was it was spinning so it wasn't like it
was it wasn't grabbing yeah but like you
hear the turbo and stuff BR and the
downshift yeah transmission's mad
aggressive
too boy what's going
oning the dude you're [__] skinny
dude you look great bro you too y yeah
dude what the [__] how does it look how
does it look look sick it looks straight
out of a movie it doesn't look real bro
so I think I think I think we should put
like set and forget [__] right here I
think we should only do it on this side
honestly look cuz if you put it that way
I feel like it's going to look rer look
so then I think I think we should put
set forget down here no yeah I generally
think that you're not you're not ready
no you're not ready really going next
get 100 bucks per ride 100 bucks per
ride yeah so today's not Tom Price to me
real quick pass it to me I was going to
just give it right back to him and be
like here's your
100 yo what the actual [__] Alex yo Slow
Down slow
down what the
[__] yo
bro I told you bro it's literally
dude this is the craziest car ever this
is insane this is my first time in a
Bugatti I learn from my stop losses not
from my take profits if something hits a
take profit that's super normal to me I
really continue with my day like that
was what supposed to happen if it hits
my stop plus I'm surprised like because
I'm really really selective with every
single trade I take and I'm not not in
the market because I can't can't wait to
make more money for brother that's that
forget Bo that
forget all right guys today might be
getting gooseb today might be the
[__] day we take a trade and we
actually win we haven't taken a trade
and one since our friend right here has
been here you know I cannot make this
[__] up yo isn't that crazy he's back
we're taking a trade right now we're
taking a trade right now Mark market
update Mark I what the hell is going on
I can't believe this thean is
back
yo isn't that crazy that's your
friend all right so market update right
now market update it is currently 9:28
in the morning we have not taken any
positions the account is still exactly
the same
$894,000 sign right there my boy okay so
let's start off with Euro GBP so
yesterday on Euro GBP we were up here at
this high and anticipated for price to
have that pullback in order for us to
actually start heading to the upside so
we're having that pullback and honestly
I don't even think I need an entry
signal I just think I need the Iguana
signal I I'll take a trade right now on
I bet guess what if I did do that I
would then have to drive the beetle
remember if I break my trading rules I
have to drive the Beetle and I don't
want to drive the beetle in the heat
here in Miami I don't want to be sweaty
I have a Bugatti I want to drive my
Bugatti chilling so this is Euro gvp
which right now we are currently waiting
for this 4our time frame to potentially
close as and go from Candlestick or you
know what we can actually take this
trade once it body closes above this
structure point right here once it does
do that if it does do that we can have a
very a very very very comfortable stop
loss of about 30 Pips under the area of
interest and then we could have our take
profit anywhere up here and this can be
a solid 1 to 2.7 risk of reward maybe I
can minimize the stop loss a little bit
more and then obviously a risk to reward
would be a lot greater but I am actively
looking to enter this trade I'm going to
put an alarm right up here uh GBP CHF
last night it did not have the body CES
the closure under the structure level
how we wanted it to uh we did hit the
alarm probably like at 1: 2 3 in the
morning I was knocked out I literally
did not even like like hear or notice
anything any of this I am still very
much interested in taking this position
so I'm going to literally set a new
alarm right down here refresh it because
this thing kind of glitches out
sometimes so we're going to set an alarm
right at the bottom of this level right
here which is going to be as soon as it
breaks into that structure but
truthfully I feel like I might just
enter this trade probably right now
because it did have the shift of
structure it did have the potential Head
and Shoulders that it's creating right
now oh man dude this is not the time for
this this is not the time to not be
moving fast come on so this is the left
the head and then the right shoulder we
did break under that structure point
this is the engulfing Candlestick right
here this is not a bad entry up here but
you know what I want something right
around here I need that extra
confirmation in order to enter that
trade so as soon as price kind of gets
to this area right here we're going to
actually enter the trade I'm going to
even add another alarm just so I get
double alarm and literally that's all we
need I don't really need to enter any
other market like obviously you know
we'll look at these markets just to
educational purposes Euro AUD we never
broke and retested above never took a
trade but the move actually did end up
happening USD CAD never retested to them
but the move did end up happening gbpusd
never had the pullback but the push
ended up happening nzdusd we were
interested never retested the move ended
up happening gvp CAD this one did not do
anything that we we wanted to this
actually going to be a very good trade
to take once it rejects up here from
this level EUR USD same thing and then
we're not interested in this market Yeah
so basically EUR GBP we're looking to
enter and GBP CHF we're looking to enter
and if we go short on GBP CHF literally
if we're selling it that means that the
pound is getting weak and if we are
buying Euro GBP that means that the
pound is getting weak so they're both
cross-correlated perfect cuz if we were
to be selling both if this Market sells
then that means that the pound is
getting strong because euro is the base
and the GBP is the quote but since
they're both basically doing the
opposite which is how it's supposed to
be that kind of confirms that this can
now potentially get strong right now and
that this can get strong right now as
well so stay tuned for market update
leave no they still there still there
oh [__] don't don't move hey don't scare
okay uh we might take this trade right
now just because of the uana and we're
going to get ready for a long day today
we got to go see Kodak Black what should
I feel like we got to gift him something
feel like we got to gift Kodak something
like I've been listening to Kodak since
I was like 15 Bo I'm about my squir you
know I've been listening to Kodak since
I didn't even have a car and I was
jamming him out now the fact that I'm
going to put my Bugatti in one of his
music videos with Donald Trump it's just
it just doesn't it doesn't feel real you
know it just it's insane to me I was
going to high school listening to the
song like yo Florida boy I like this guy
it's cool and obviously he blew up I was
listening to Kodak when he was not big
at all I was just believing in him you
know I'm like supporting him and then he
took off and now it's kind of weird how
the whole thing reconnects I don't know
it's I I I I wouldn't know how to
explain what's about to happen right now
so it's about to be a very long day all
I can say is let him forget patience P
well obviously we just patience P my
boys it's all thanks to you when you
when you catch a trade like the one that
I'm in right now who the [__] is call oh
this is the Trump thing so uh quick
update we we had a move the shoot to
tomorrow morning um it's 100% tomorrow
morning I'm not sure if that's still
going to work with you guys and sorry
for the last minute change we're just
been coordinating with all the artists
and everything trade update we are in GB
EF as you guys can see we're currently
up about $6,000 so we entered this trade
earlier literally probably like [__]
I don't know like an hour ago but we're
in the middle of all these cause and the
trade is now heading into our Direction
everything's looking very well we're
actually in a lot more profit than I
expected obviously I did not account how
volatile this pair is I did not realize
that if this pair goes into a little bit
more draw down we'll blow this account
completely cuz this pair is super
volatile I actually have not entered a
trade in GP CHF in a very long time but
this trade right here if it does does
hit my takeprofit it could take this
account up to like $70,000 if it does
make it all the way down here so we're
in our trade Euro GBP which is the other
position currently is actually having
the push as well but I likeed GBP CHF
better so with that being said set and
forget so no video shoot with Kodak
Black today you guys can see this is how
it is with these celebrities bro it's
always they're always changing times
always changing dates it's part of the
pro
So today we're probably just going to
now change our whole entire schedule hit
the gym and see where the day takes us
so stay tuned when are we going to you
know drift the Bugatti yeah so we got to
go drift the Bugatti dude but I want to
drift it when it's raining cuz it's like
I don't it's a Bugatti you know what I'm
saying I'm a Savage I don't care I'll do
whatever but I got to be a little bit
more intelligent and mature about this
decision it's it's going to get done but
it's going to be
done calculated everything we do is very
calculated and structured and I don't
want to just do it crazy cuz it's like
dude an ax on a Bugatti is probably like
$150,000 that's fine no big deal problem
is the time down it'll be down for like
3 months waiting for that part to come
in and all that stuff
so we'll update you guys all right trade
update trade
update still in the same spot we have
not moved at all account is literally
exactly the same actually never mind we
are actually up about
$7,000 nap
time I'm honestly concerned with that
face it's a good face cuz the Iguana was
here oh [__] it
left I don't know if we should close the
position now cuz we're up
$177,000 on this trade let's [__] go
literally pass the take profit that we
had for the week the week goal that we
had was make 16,000 balance balance
we're currently
$26,000 in profit and truthfully we were
actually up more we're probably around
like: 30 but it's 5:00 right now as you
can see right here 5:00 5:00 p.m. EST
and the spread at this time is insane so
let me show you guys literally from
exactly where we entered the trade
little to no draw down straight right
into profit daily time frame has closed
absolutely beautifully engulfing and now
we are simply going to expect for price
to have a little pullback and then
continue heading to the downside all
we're going to do is simply set and
forget now next trade is Euro gvp which
it also had the move exactly as we've
been anticipating we didn't actually
enter this trade we were just watching
it but it is playing out so this trade
is looking very solid um I could expect
the 4H hour to come back retest this
neckline here before actually heading
back to the downside so we have to be on
the lookout for that pullback so for now
nothing else that we can do other than
just what should we do now I think let's
go hit the city let's go have a quick
lunch at the city maybe gym and see
where the trade goes okay
but when are we drifting the Bugatti
we're going to drift it when it's
raining trust me when it starts raining
we're going to drift it I promise I keep
my word with everything remember it just
it hasn't rained look at the weather it
looks like it's going to rain but it
hasn't let's go hit the city let's go
flex a little
[Music]
bit ladies and gentlemen we are finally
back home long long day in the city uh
we might move to the city soon I might
be a city boy very soon but not
confirmed just yet currently 11:20 at
night market update the account is
currently sitting at drum roll
please
$38,000 Ching well right now I think
this trade is that's why I'm not even
that excited because I do think this
trade right now in London session is
going to have a pullback let me show you
so I think now this is will have a
retracement to retest this neckline of
the left head right shoulder for then
the trade to then head to the downside
currently on the daily time frame we
Clos very strong as a bearish engulfing
but we could come back and retest these
daily Wicks right here so then the trade
can continue heading to the downside now
this is where a lot of beginner Traders
will probably get you know fomo and you
their close out their positions here or
they can probably set and forget the
whole entire way currently just waiting
for it to do its thing Euro gvp had its
pushup once again I think it could have
another type of quick pullback before
actually having the push to the upside
GBP CHF is the one where we're actually
in and if it does have a pullback once
it is in here I'm going to be
determining whether I you know cut my
loss a little bit short or I set them
forget because if that trade goes a
little bit into draw down we will blow
the account and we're going to have to
start all over I am not trying to start
all over so I'm going to make sure that
I can do this appropriately So currently
right now 11:20 at night we're going to
now probably go take a shower and just
look at the charge through the phones
throughout the whole entire night and
see what happens tomorrow in the morning
so we'll update you guys in the
morning all right guys good morning
trade update it is currently 9:16 and in
the morning kind of stayed up last night
to like 2: 3 in the morning pretty much
for no reason exactly what I explained
that was going to happen happened we are
currently back up to drum roll
please
$32,000 and profit how much were we up
yesterday about the same right yeah
about the same not exciting on all but
technicals are exciting so yesterday if
you noticed we were down here at this
Candlestick and I explained that we had
to have this retracement in order for
price to continue heading to the
downside exactly what we did now we're
having that retracement to now
potentially continue heading to the
downside now this is key to
understanding that this draw down or
Draw down or losing some profits had to
happen in order for this trade to now
create that new lower leg push this
might sound crazy but I would actually
would have liked if it came up a lot
further because then I confirmed that it
would reject this neckline of this head
and shoulders of support support support
then use as resistance and then if it
has the push now I somewhat know that it
would never come back up there so now
that it didn't make it there there's a
little Gap and they can potentially fill
that Gap so that is a little bit of a
red flag but we'll be fine next is Euro
GBP same exact thing it's having the
pullback just how I explained now we
should have a reaction from this point
now before actually heading to the
upside so basically the only trade that
we're in right now is and interested in
is GBP CHF and we're just expecting for
this to continue heading to the downside
so there's not much else to do other
than S and forget so today is day day
two trying to pull up to this music
video with Trump and Kodak and oh and
now they're going to add AB Antonio
Brown um into the mix crazy right I I
don't I don't ask questions problem the
problem with all these celebrities is
that they're not organized they're just
all over the place very normal in the
industry and they're just Changing Times
moving locations and I'm just kind of on
standby which is kind of annoying
because I got a bunch of [__] to do and
I'm kind of just moving things around to
make this happen so we'll update you if
we actually end up doing it but now they
changed from yesterday to today in the
morning and now last night they sent a
message hey we're going to change the
time from the morning to another time
that we'll update in the morning like
all right all right I'm okay
so right now currently up 32,000
I think it went a little lower sad I
forget so you're telling me you're going
to turn $100 into a
[Music]
million no [__] way no wig so you're
taller than LeBron I'm like 6'2 How much
taller are you than him I don't know
maybe we're using different metrics I
copy trade you but instead 10x that and
I put in $1,000 I'll make $10 million
I'll put you dude some guy started with
5K and he's already up
158 and I'm only up at I'm at 22,000
look my trade I just literally at 22,000
this is not going in the commercial for
whatever this is I don't want to be no
look prove this guy wrong look so I
started off with 100 bucks okay and I
scaled scaled scaled and I'm at 22,000
right
now okay but there I saw some red in
yeah I took losses of course yeah I loss
is part of the game I took two losses my
wins that away my loss you have you have
to take this is a big comeback right
here yeah that's two negative days but
then a big swing back on six you were
were you sweating right there little bit
Yeah so wait if you fail start again I
failed it's be like but if you fail that
means everyone else with you failed
that's part of the game bro but that's
so much I know it's a lot of but you're
only starting with 100
bucks you are well whoever if people
want to start with more that's not my
problem yeah that's fair like that's
just crazy
pressure cuz if you think about you're
not trading for only yourself all your
guys are trading for yeah like all of my
videos right now and literally like by
the end of the week they all have
150,000 views by the end of the
[Music]
week this wouldn't be suspicious if it
wasn't a Bugatti
look I got some cash for you
bro that's a bit extra but so I have 500
and hundreds and I got 10
one you can do whatever you want with
this there's a there's a place I know
you could go yeah you got a boy trap
right here on the comment say I know
Alex They Know You by name thank you
very much good morning ladies and
gentlemen yesterday I don't know if you
can tell about my face was a very long
[__] day biggest waste of time ever
nobody showed up you know what I am
literally not surprised that is how [__]
goes when you go do events with people
like this now today they're calling me
yo pull up please pull up you got
another today they're going to actually
show up I'm like dude I'm not I don't
think I'm going to go I don't think I'm
going to go key word cuz a picture with
Trump and
Kodak like you just don't get that ever
again you know so Cent
ly we have hit the goal for the week
turning $100 into a million where we are
now currently at a
$222,000 balance now remember we started
off the week wanting to take $8,000 up
to
$116,000 now I'm not as excited because
I saw $35,000 on the balance at one
point now I the reason why I closed the
position and I didn't set and forget is
simply because yesterday and of the
commotion we were supposed to like not
have our our phones and I didn't want to
not be able to look at it so as this
trade was pulling back up into this area
I saw potential for this to actually
have a push up through here and actually
make it through this daily area of
interest and then make it back up to
retest this level of Support over here
and this level of resistance to actually
retest round psychological level 1.1
2500 as you can see it looks like the
daily has created a higher low higher
high looks like it's creating a higher
low right now retesting that structure
and it could be the push to actually
make it up into this area to then have
the push because technically it hasn't
quite made it there just yet so for now
kind of sucks because I do want to be in
this position and truthfully entering
this position now it's literally not
that far from our original entry it's
literally just 13 Pips so I'm going to
definitely be on the lookout to enter
this position again I was just kind of
confused thinking that you know what if
we're not going to have our phones they
got to move us everywhere and I got to
do something here I got to just make
sure I I I could lock in my stuff know
the president's pulling up to some place
trust me it's Secret Service not [__]
around so Euro GBP though we completely
avoided this loss right here this loss
was completely avoided on the initial
push on the pullback just a loss avoided
as a whole and it's kind of it's quite
interesting because this is actually one
of the top trades that I had set for
myself up for this week weekly time
frame looks reasonable looks like it
could actually make it all the way back
to that structure point so this will be
a pair that we'll be interested in for
next week this never happened oh you
know what I'll do another video on
Instagram now to show people and educate
people on why we avoided this loss Euro
Au currently having that pullback that
we were anticipating after having a
reaction from the structure level not
interested in it GBP CAD just continuing
having the push to the upside USD CAD
just continuing having the push to the
downside
gbpusd continuing to have the push to
the upside which is insane nzdusd had
the push never stopped and then Euro USD
just continued to have the push to the
upside so literally the only pair that
is still somewhat looking good is GBP
CHF and I'm going to be waiting for a
new added entry position on this
sometime very very very very soon
so not super stoked because we actually
had more money into the accounts and
because I am tired dude we've been like
I think for the last 2 weeks every
single day except Saturday or Sunday
we've been sleeping 2 three hours every
single day and that [__] just builds up
you know
so I don't know I S for good all right
so in a day like today not such a sunny
great day got to make the most out of it
so body owner like myself take an opport
like this to potentially see if it could
drift I went on YouTube I searched up
how to drift the B nothing came up no
way in their life and tri to the guy
especially the pink guy but you know
what you got to be your first some
somebody's got to do
[Music]
we [__] did it yo we just blew the
whole [__] account no that's how you
closed the trade
bro it literally just blew
the
whole
account F we just withdrew all the money
so we just draw the money from the
current broker should get into my wallet
by the end of today maybe tomorrow and
uh we're going to deposit into a new
broker which I might be letting you guys
soon which broker it's going to be so
you guys are going to have the same
market conditions as me current broker
right now the fees were all over the
price the commissions were okay it was
more of the slippage I would literally
try and close a trade out I get slipped
out I wouldn't get close at the point
that I wanted to so I'm going to be
switching to a new broker today pretty
much and uh we'll see where the
challenge goes from that point sucks
that we're not in this position anymore
so gbpchf is still exactly in the same
spot I could anticipate maybe a little
bit of another Pool back here before
heading up to the downside tonight so
let's see if the deposit hits by today
so that I can enter this position London
session tonight so I will update you
guys then see you guys we're [__]
back I can't even explain
why we're [__]
back here goes uh so we just got here
at
10 kodak's not here yet we'll probably
be here in like 30 minutes we going to
leave to like 3 in the
[Music]
morning on this side right quick my bad
wait hold on hold on hold on hold I'm
not going to lie this [__] feels a
little too wobbly
[Music]
we are still here 9 a.m. basically a
trade update and we're still
here well after a couple
hours finally got it
up now we got to take it from this P
truck to that to
Tru [__] this
D this is real life man [__] can I give
you the bird
yeah oh we're just show should we show
them doesn't matter I guess you show
them it doesn't matter right well this
is all I'm going to show right here the
beginning of this video start off with
my new Bugatti now you may ask yourself
this guy can't buy any more cars he has
10 11 cars how can you buy another car
well I did I bought another car and I'm
going tell you right now I just upped
the Bugatti
in rareness right not so much price for
me to up the
Bugatti I'd have to sell my cat and I
have to I'd have to sell you I'd have to
sell everything all right cuz uping up
the Bugatti is $6 million right it's
it's uh you know I could do it
but I'm going be eating Ramen no for the
rest of my life no it just won't be a
smart financial decision but I did buy a
new car and all I can say is I wish show
you guys next week so with that being
said let me show you guys how this week
has ended exactly what I said exactly
what I said market update GBP CHF we
Clos out the trade around this level
around here simply because I strongly
predicted that price is going to have a
pullback and retest this level and that
the weekly time frame was not done
having the pullback can expect for price
to have a push up into this area and and
then as soon as you get there then have
the rejection price has to stop for
about a week how it did here price
pushed stopped and then the next week it
had the push same exact thing here price
had the push stop retracement so on and
so forth price has the push stop then
push price has the push stop then push
that's what we are anticipating for this
week to come ahead so we avoided not
making any money this week simply
because we have experience in the market
you can have the best trading strategy
which is simply mine set and forget I'm
done throwing you know little shots that
make it it's the best it's just the
reality situation not up for discussion
anymore ICT SCM MCC all you ICT and MC
Traders while you guys watching this
video right
now ICT so
good and and smart money whatever is so
good H well no comment no
so had to get that out here I feel so
good getting out that my chest cuz all
the icts are the best what are you guys
doing here huh exactly gotcha so s foret
is number one no longer out for
discussion even you having the best
strategy you need to have time and
experience to truly know what is going
to happen next in the market because you
are in sync with the market you just
understand it like I've seen this
pattern happen so many times in the
market structure yes you can have the
Hoin St strategy checklist everything
makes sense to 100% but then you just
looking at it it doesn't look right it
just doesn't look like it's ready for
the move it needs that next step and the
only way you can actually determine that
is by experience and that's exactly what
we just showed you guys here how
experience led me to closing out the
trade at the perfect point before it
went into my stop-loss area so yeah this
week we are already going to deposit the
new $22,000 in into the account for next
week so you guys can see the $22,000
have been retrieved from the account so
we're going to deposit into a new broker
test it out if we like it I'm going to
be sharing the broker with you guys so
you guys can simply use it and every
single one of these trades I want you
guys to have this extremely clear I
share with my students every single week
on Sunday swings I get on a call with
them I give them my top two top three
pairs that I'm going to be trading for
the week ahead I literally give you guys
trading signals but it's a lot better
than a signals because a signal you just
get a text message enter here stop loss
take profit figure it out no this is
different we got an Zoom call oneon-one
where you can ask me questions you can
get your questions answered every single
week and I'm literally explaining to you
my whole thought process behind the
trade if I just send you a signal
there's no thought process you just kind
of have to figure it out I'm giving you
a full-blown one twoh hour call where I
go into detail why explaining on it and
Sunday swings is part of the set and
forget strategy in the set and forget
Community which if you want to know more
about it the link is description below
because not a lot of people understand
how set and forget has chained thousands
of lives out there literally every
single week students are catching these
trades alongside with me it's not just
me so if you guys want to know more
about s and forget click the link in
description if you want to join sunay it
comes included with the education
platform with the community with the
psychology series everything is in one
I'm not these kind of guys that sells
everything separate I hate doing that
once you're part of the set and forget
community that is for life so if you
guys want to be part of these trades and
be on a call with me every single week
join set don't forget and I'll see you
this Sunday with that being said Wick
seeks Wick
seeks dude I'm so fried I'm so tired
it's been a long day dude it's been a
long [__] week you hear the cat
crying cat somewhere in this
house I jump
off honestly I think if I jump off it
won't be that bad don't
hurt you do it first
no all right so you guys want to join
instead don't forget click the link
description below week six was very
successful and the week 7 the goal is to
take
$22,000 now to
$40,000 boys we're getting at that point
we're now we're about a couple flips
away to being from 100 to a qu mil qu
mil half a mil half a mil A Millie hit
that like And subscribe button I'll see
you in the next video